

PROFILE

Innovative and deadline-driven Full Stack Developer with a strong background in .NET.

After spending 13 years in the medical device field selling surgical robotic systems, I became more interested in the software and technology that drove these systems than making a sale. Becoming a software developer was the next logical step and challenge in my life.

Please feel free to visit my portfolio website listed below to explore my Issue Tracker and Blog, which were created using C# and the .NET framework.

CONTACT

PHONE: 410-274-1554

WEBSITE:

https://erichartjen.netlify.app/

EMAIL:

Eric.A.Hartjen@Gmail.com

ERIC HARTJEN

https://erichartjen.netlify.app/

EDUCATION

University of Florida, Warrington College of Business, Gainesville, Florida June 2004 – June 2008 Bachelor of Science in Business Administration, June 2008 Business management Major

WORK EXPERIENCE

Coder Foundry, Junior .Net Developer

July 2021 - Current

Created multiple projects in the .NET stack to include:

Issue Tracker (https://bugtracker-application.herokuapp.com)

- Enterprise level issue tracking software
- .NET 5 MVC Application
- Deployed to Heroku using CI/CD
- PostgreSQL database
- Code First database development using Entity Framework Core
- Role and Identity based security

Personal Blog (https://ehartjen-blog.herokuapp.com)

- Personal Blogging CMS
- .NET 5 MVC Application
- Role based Security
- Deployed to Heroku using CI/CD

Medtronic Spine & Biologics, Sales Representative

October 2016 - June 2021

FRAMEWORKS & PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML5
.NET
Bootstrap
C#
ASP.NET
CSS3
JavaScript
MVC
LINQ
SQL